JOE WIGLEY



joekwigley@aol.com



07943 054 460



inkedin.com/in/joe-wigley-304296108

SKILLS

Web Development Design | Publication

GitHub HTML CSS3 Javascript | JQuery | Foundation Photoshop Invision Lightroom IMovie

MAMP MySQL Oracle 12C Wordpress Visual Studio Code

Filezilla

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Joe, I am an aspiring web developer currently studying part time at the University of Northampton, when I am not working or studying you can find me at the gym or a lot of the time, eating! I'm a big food guy. If I'm not eating though I'm usually shoulder deep under the bonnet of my car. I'm a massive petrol head and love anything car or bike related, in fact, I'd rather go on a track day then go on holiday! Learning new things is a must for me, and it can be related to anything, car, motorbike or coding, but I like to stay up to date.

Below is a summary of work for the last 10 years.

EMPLOYMENT

EVENTS CONSULTANT, Conference 08/2011 – Present Care Ltd.

- Deliver outstanding customer service via all communication channels.
- Handling enquiries from a wide range of customers and taking the time to identify the key factors that will make their event a success.
- Support the client through the full enquiry process including using my venue knowledge to assist them in creating a shortlist of venues.
- Client Negotiations: Conducting intense negotiations with venues to secure our clients the best possible rates available along with complimentary added values.
 - Where applicable multiyear deal negotiations are entered into.
- Company Negotiations: Entering into negotiations with the venue on behalf of our directors to obtain increased commission levels, payment terms and contract terms and conditions.
- Cross selling Event Management, Team Building and Audio Visual Equipment.
- Approaching customer complaints in a professional and understanding manor whilst complying with company protocol but still ensuring the customer is pleased with the outcome.
- Working alongside the Conference Care event management team onsite to ensure the client's expectations are exceeded and to help the event run as smooth as possible.

 Cross checking, amending, approving and signing legal contracts on behalf of Conference Care's contracted clients and arranging payment via various methods.

After 2 years at Conference Care (July 2013) I was awarded a promotion from Reservations Advisor to Events Consultant. In January 2016 I was given the sole responsibility of looking after all of the audio visual & system elements within the business in addition to being in charge of the maintenance and update of the commission structure.

SALES EXECUTIVE & SERVICE ADVISOR, 09/2008 – 08/2011 Robins and Day Peugeot Birmingham Central

- Overcoming objections from customers to clinch the sale.
- Working with the team to market our cars successfully creating new custom whilst retaining repeat business.
- Administration of quotes and legally binding contracts.
- Achieving individual and team sales targets by ensuring our customers received the very best customer service at all times.
- Upselling additional products during the after sales process.
- Booking in the vehicles for their required service, monitoring the progress of the repair and reporting back any additional work that was required.
- Handling complaints in a time effective manor and ensuring protocol was adhered to at all times.

SALES ADVISOR, Midland Reprographics 03/2008 – 09/2008

Please Note: This was a temporary position during non-college days.

- Travelling the Midlands region to various workplaces to sell the companies services which specialise in selling and operating maintenance contracts for office machines such as multi-function printers and documenting solutions.
- Using my persistence and initiative I worked hard to secure appointments with new potential clients.
- Once I had engaged my client I used my proactive sales skills, personality and negotiation skills to then secure the contract for the company whilst ensuring my client was provided with a service that would suit their needs.
- During my time at Midland Reprographic I achieved my sales targets each week and created several new contracts for the company which they have since retained.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NORTHAMPTON 10/2017 – 04/2020

Part time study, HND Business Computing (Web Design)

NORTH WARWICKSHIRE AND HINCKLEY COLLEGE

09/2007 - 06/2009

B-Tec Diploma in Business Studies

REFERENCES

Liz Coulter-Smith Christopher Peacock

Senior Lecturer Computing Conference Care
University of Northampton I Watling House

Watling Drive Hinckley Leicestershire LEI0 3EY

liz.coulter-smith@northampton.ac.uk chrisp@conferencecare.com